Guide to the C. D. Wright Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2007 Acquisition, 1955-2006; 17.58; (26 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  - Oversize
    - Arkansas, 1985-1990, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Forrest Gander, 1983-1986, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Essays, not included in collection, 1990-1993, undated (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Brown University papers, 1986-1991; 2 (Box 19 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous magazines, 1985-1996 (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Essays, 1978-1990 (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1990-1993 (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Invisible City, String Light, 1980-1991 (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous notes and postcards, 1962-1989, undated (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Work correspondence, 1977-1995, undated (Box 20 (Oversize))
    - Poetry Center 1980, 1980-1982 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Books collected for Map, 2000, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Press, 1998 August 12 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Barataria #2, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Peru, etc., 1999, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Press packet/CD/Georgia/original, 1990-1992, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Essay on form, AWP, 1989-1990, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Russia, 1987-1991, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Art, 1979-1997, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Film, 1978-1984, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Music/dance theater, 1978-1988, undated (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - Angola - news clippings re: crime, 2000-2006 (Box 21 (Oversize))
    - One Big Self, exhibition, reviews, cost, expenses, 2003-2005 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - OBS, 2005, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Lannan Award, 1999-2002 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Tremble, reviews, 1996-1998, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - har (related to terrorism articles), 2001 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Reviews CD, 1979-1987 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Photocopies and printouts of articles, 1994-1997, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Tremble, reviews, 1997-2000 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - String Light, reviews, 1991-1994 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Deepstep, 1998-2000, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Anthologies, 1980-1998, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Residencies, etc, 1993-2001, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - ECCO, 1995-1997, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Greenfield Recorder - Gazette, 1957 September 6 (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - Fliers, letters, pamphlets, 1984-2000, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - 2000, 2000, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - 1999, 1999, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - 1998, 1998, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - 1997, 1997, undated (Box 22 (Oversize))
    - 1996, 1996, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1994, 1994, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1990, 1990, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1989, 1989, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1987, 1987, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1986, 1986, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1984, 1984, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - 1983, 1983, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - Newspaper, printed material, 1986-2001, undated (Box 23 (Oversize))
    - Files from LRP, 1994-1997, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Recent LRP, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Maps, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Arkansas, 1996, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Historical Maps of Arkansas, 1993, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Miscellaneous, 1994-1996, undated (Box 24 (Oversize))
    - Maps, undated (Box 25 (Broadside))
  - Computer Media
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted Fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Lila Wallace 3a copy of 2 disk full 11-3.93/11-1693, 2007-ycal-4686-0001; 1 (Box 26)
      Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - lila wallace 2 Aug 10 93 copy updated 9-4-93 12-21-93 8-10-95 addit. Disk full, 2007-ycal-4686-0002; 1 (Box 26)
    - LR Project feb 28 94 add 8-10-95 disk full, 2007-ycal-4686-0003; 1 (Box 26)
    - Lila Wallace, 2007-ycal-4686-0004; 1 (Box 26)
    - Lost roads project off hard drive last installment proj MIS., 2007-ycal-4686-0005; 1 (Box 26)
    - Lost Roads Project -files for taut -spoken word guide, 2007-ycal-4686-0006; 1 (Box 26)
    - broadsides profiles b'side list essay Old, 2007-ycal-4686-0007; 1 (Box 26)
    - Sept 94 misc grab beg hua. grant narrat. Nov 1995 Lila Wallace still, 2007-ycal-4686-0008; 1 (Box 26)
    - BG 1, 2007-ycal-4686-0009; 1 (Box 26)
    - unreadable in CD PBr cooling Time 1-9-97, 1-10 2-19-97 3-12-97 add [illegible] 3-26 3-28 add [illegible] 3-28, 2007-ycal-4686-0010; 1 (Box 26)
    - everything off HD/ pb 1400 copied est. pb 64, 2007-ycal-4686-0011; 1 (Box 26)
    - Cooling Time (Palatino) 5-28-97 10-12-97 10-24-97, 2007-ycal-4686-0012; 1 (Box 26)
    - cooling time 5-16-97 4-17-97 5-25-97 cooling time (mostly) corrected long version 8-6-97, 2007-ycal-4686-0013; 1 (Box 26)
    - Applications E AB elect. add. book, 2007-ycal-4686-0014; 1 (Box 26)
    - THE LEAVES IN HER SHOES JLJACOBS (ALSO CREDITS) old version, 2007-ycal-4686-0015; 1 (Box 26)
    - LRP Project odds + ends deep step poetry mo/schedule, 2007-ycal-4686-0016; 1 (Box 26)
    - The Interviews The Interviews Lost Roads Project, 2007-ycal-4686-0017; 1 (Box 26)
    - lila wallace fi goo, 2007-ycal-4686-0018; 1 (Box 26)
    - taggart / berger send p.s., 2007-ycal-4686-0019; 1 (Box 26)
    - [illegible], 2007-ycal-4686-0020; 1 (Box 26)
    - CD's edit Endas foo, 2007-ycal-4686-0021; 1 (Box 26)
    - Josie's short + long things, 2007-ycal-4686-0022; 1 (Box 26)
    - taggart has credit line (send p.s. on hard drive in gale's office), 2007-ycal-4686-0023; 1 (Box 26)
    - Tremble 1-21-95 1-29-95 2-2-95, 2007-ycal-4686-0024; 1 (Box 26)
    - law school one C.D. From Josie, 2007-ycal-4686-0025; 1 (Box 26)
    - POEMS DISK Tremble 3 Whistle 3 3(sent) 2 Tremble 1/19/93 working file The Passenger Debbie the last words, 2007-ycal-4686-0026; 1 (Box 26)
    - gale nelson jim harms rostoul salary letter fundraising tled; inp search BUSINESS DISK passenger building 1 cochran 2 bob c Lila wallace foley lila 2 directory lila 3 budget leave request Whitehead taggart funds waiting lease helium, 2007-ycal-4686-0027; 1 (Box 26)
    - C.V. -- CD Wright C.V. + bio update 12-7-96 10-31-97, 2007-ycal-4686-0028; 1 (Box 26)
    - Tremble june 94 6-16 hard disk. girlfriend has new [illegible] but refer to 6-1 for corrections too, 2007-ycal-4686-0029; 1 (Box 26)
    - correspondence 1994-1995, 2007-ycal-4686-0030; 1 (Box 26)
    - Spg 95 Dec 95 CV etc. Tremble 2-2-95 -bio adv cl. list cv innov. syl., 2007-ycal-4686-0031; 1 (Box 26)
    - The Leaves in Her Shoes converted 27 July 98 Jacobs, 2007-ycal-4686-0032; 1 (Box 26)
    - Poetry month LRP contribution letter June 1996, 2007-ycal-4686-0033; 1 (Box 26)
    - interview w/RbSeth -statement of goals -faculty bulletin -interview in RW + CM, 2007-ycal-4686-0034; 1 (Box 26)
    - disinfectant, 2007-ycal-4686-0035; 1 (Box 26)
    - Lost Roads Pubs., 2007-ycal-4686-0036; 1 (Box 26)
    - hp deskjet 350 installation, 2007-ycal-4686-0037; 1 (Box 26)
    - brother Disk 1 of 2 Version B TextBridge OCR by XEROX, 2007-ycal-4686-0038; 1 (Box 26)
    - brother Disk 2 of 2 Version B TextBridge OCR by XEROX, 2007-ycal-4686-0039; 1 (Box 26)
    - Mule Reserve Poetry 7-98, 2007-ycal-4686-0040; 1 (Box 26)
    - Battlefield 5-99, 6-99 Adirondacks + Vermont disk Herd Notes + Bestey 8-31-99, 2007-ycal-4686-0041; 1 (Box 26)
    - Brother Multi-Function Link for Microsoft Windows Disk 1 Version B, 2007-ycal-4686-0042; 1 (Box 26)
    - Brother Multi-Function Link for Microsoft Windows Disk 2 Version B, 2007-ycal-4686-0043; 1 (Box 26)
    - [no label information], 2007-ycal-4686-0044; 1 (Box 26)
    - Even More Fonts! LaserWriter, 2007-ycal-4686-0045; 1 (Box 26)
    - More Fonts… LaserWriter, 2007-ycal-4686-0046; 1 (Box 26)
    - Disk 1 Personal LaserWriter NTR Macintosh Installation, 2007-ycal-4686-0047; 1 (Box 26)
    - Disk 3 Personal LaserWriter NTR Macintosh Printer Software, 2007-ycal-4686-0048; 1 (Box 26)
    - Disk 2 Personal LaserWriter NTR Macintosh Printer Software, 2007-ycal-4686-0049; 1 (Box 26)
    - Eudora E-mail, 2007-ycal-4686-0050; 1 (Box 26)
    - Truitt promo matter, 2007-ycal-4686-0051; 1 (Box 26)
    - Iowa City files incop. adv. spg 98 Syllabus, 2007-ycal-4686-0052; 1 (Box 26)
    - new poems + other writing A Brown computer, 2007-ycal-4686-0053; 1 (Box 26)
    - letters + business C.D. search delay, 2007-ycal-4686-0054; 1 (Box 26)
    - Disk #1 1.2 MB. Anamok/osis Eisenhower, 2007-ycal-4686-0055; 1 (Box 26)
    - Wright.C Wright.Q, 2007-ycal-4686-0056; 1 (Box 26)
    - DW 300 C D Wright, 2007-ycal-4686-0057; 1 (Box 26)
    - letters - pres. (Brown), 2007-ycal-4686-0058; 1 (Box 26)
    - poetics disk artlines (postits) Tremble 1-19-93 2-22-93 Tremble 4 6-1-94 Tremble 5 Jan 8 95 error, 2007-ycal-4686-0059; 1 (Box 26)
    - MacSlip (1), 2007-ycal-4686-0060; 1 (Box 26)
    - josiah, 2007-ycal-4686-0061; 1 (Box 26)
    - MacSlip MacSlip It[illegible] Bran T[illegible] MacSlip D[illegible] MacSlip Apple [illegible], 2007-ycal-4686-0062; 1 (Box 26)
    - 1995 fall syllabus - grad wkshop seminar - radical of poetry of everyday life fall questionnaire-recs fall 95, 2007-ycal-4686-0063; 1 (Box 26)
    - misc. Aug 26 96-- lila wallace letter re: selection con. olde syllabus, 2007-ycal-4686-0064; 1 (Box 26)
    - Mis -- everything Brown hd questionnaire, 2007-ycal-4686-0065; 1 (Box 26)
    - misc. (many recs), 2007-ycal-4686-0066; 1 (Box 26)
    - [no label information], 2007-ycal-4686-0067; 1 (Box 26)
    - [no label information], 2007-ycal-4686-0068; 1 (Box 26)
    - [no label information], 2007-ycal-4686-0069; 1 (Box 26)
    - [no label information], 2007-ycal-4686-0070; 1 (Box 26)
    - GAMES Prince of Persia Emily's Games, 2007-ycal-4686-0071; 1 (Box 26)
    - MacComCenter fax and data communications, 2007-ycal-4686-0072; 1 (Box 26)
    - Interim Pool Report, 2007-ycal-4686-0073; 1 (Box 26)
    - Dw 6.0, 2007-ycal-4686-0074; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up disk 7, 2007-ycal-4686-0075; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up disk 9, 2007-ycal-4686-0076; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up disk 11, 2007-ycal-4686-0077; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up Disk 10, 2007-ycal-4686-0078; 1 (Box 26)
    - Systems Back up Disk 2, 2007-ycal-4686-0079; 1 (Box 26)
    - Systems Backup Disk 3, 2007-ycal-4686-0080; 1 (Box 26)
    - Systems Back up Disk 4, 2007-ycal-4686-0081; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up Disk 5, 2007-ycal-4686-0082; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up Disk 6, 2007-ycal-4686-0083; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up Disk 8, 2007-ycal-4686-0084; 1 (Box 26)
    - Back up Disk 12, 2007-ycal-4686-0085; 1 (Box 26)
    - BACK UP DISK 13/Systems, 2007-ycal-4686-0086; 1 (Box 26)
    - BACK UP DISK 14/Systems, 2007-ycal-4686-0087; 1 (Box 26)
    - CD Rom Setup Version 5.3.2, 2007-ycal-4686-0088; 1 (Box 26)
    - Systems / Back up Disk 1, 2007-ycal-4686-0089; 1 (Box 26)
    - baby x Curka '90 mex_in x newform hills winter okla exercise Georgia Memoir 1st 45p., 2007-ycal-4686-0090; 1 (Box 27)
    - lover halperin Oct 87 junction cv update pennrw planks full Quinn quinn book chptrs b.dwk additions 88 May, 2007-ycal-4686-0091; 1 (Box 27)
    - Tuscany poseidon 1 Journal-tuscany 2 Journalism newblue corr II organica, 2007-ycal-4686-0092; 1 (Box 27)
    - LR catalog 88 the box this comes in hungrymind statement newblue2 corrections for II no good anymore, 2007-ycal-4686-0093; 1 (Box 27)
    - Lane-proposal WS bunting bio Lazartigles no more saving on this, 2007-ycal-4686-0094; 1 (Box 27)
    - Helicon 9 disk full raccoon dhill ProJoGaz Rikki ProjoRea WoodAge poetics raccoon Norton Trotsky Mayes- rec Barg Adamnt. Lane Shirley/Michael vitae [illegible] M. Williams, 2007-ycal-4686-0095; 1 (Box 27)
    - Connell memoir p46- Letters: Mayes love poem - just whistle (draft), 2007-ycal-4686-0096; 1 (Box 27)
    - Juna Os[illegible] M Tarses I May poems, letters, etc. Morrow Miss Rev Poetry East, 2007-ycal-4686-0097; 1 (Box 27)
    - didn't take, 2007-ycal-4686-0098; 1 (Box 27)
    - bluedick Dec 87, 2007-ycal-4686-0099; 1 (Box 27)
    - Blue Dick #2 p.78- *, 2007-ycal-4686-0100; 1 (Box 27)
    - New Blue Dick July 88 newblue1, 2007-ycal-4686-0101; 1 (Box 27)
    - newblue2 original July 88, 2007-ycal-4686-0102; 1 (Box 27)
    - new blue 1 #11 copy July 88, 2007-ycal-4686-0103; 1 (Box 27)
    - newblue2 copy, 2007-ycal-4686-0104; 1 (Box 27)
    - bluedick #2 copy, 2007-ycal-4686-0105; 1 (Box 27)
    - EMAIL 1-5-06 CDWright, 2007-ycal-4686-0106; 1 (Box 27)
    - CDW Desktop 1-8-06, 2007-ycal-4686-0107; 1 (Box 27)
    - email sent items to 4-26-06 gen writing bus, 2007-ycal-4686-0108; 1 (Box 27)
- January 2007 Addition, 1994-2006; 0.63; (2 boxes)
  The January 2007 Addition consists of thirty-three notebooks dating from 1994 to 2006.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 981.
  Purchased from Lame Duck Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke and Hilda Doolittle Fund book funds, 2007.
  - Notebooks, undated; 26 (Box 28)
  - Notebooks, 1994-2006, undated; 7 (Box 29)
- August 2012 Acquisition, 1966-2012; 1.5; (3 boxes)
  Box 32 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  The August 2012 acquisition contains additional correspondence, writings, printed materials, and personal papers relating chiefly to C. D. Wright's literary and professional activities.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1288.
  - Poetry Now, 1973-1982 (Box 30)
  - Harpers Bazaar magazine, 1970 August (Box 30)
  - Arkansas Times magazine, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Anthologies, 1970-1986, undated (Box 30)
  - Bibliography bio, 1971-1993, undated (Box 30)
  - Brigham, 1967, undated (Box 30)
  - Copy/Contrib by BB Monk's pond #3, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Roy W CD + correspondence Forrest, 1994-1996, undated (Box 30)
  - Coffee House Press, 1998-1999, undated (Box 30)
  - (Correspondences & notes) reference Keith & HeLouise Wilson, 1994-2000 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence w Loree Rackstraw, 1971-1995, undated (Box 30)
  - Firebird Heart, undated; 2 (Box 30)
  - Interviews, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Heaved Knopf permissions, 1997-1999, undated (Box 30)
  - Photo (Brigham Roy & Besmilr), undated (Box 30)
  - 1960s publications, 1966-1969, undated (Box 30)
  - Initial selection from 60s, 1966-1969, undated (Box 30)
  - 1970s publications, 1968-1971, undated (Box 30)
  - 1971-1972 publications, 1971-1972, undated (Box 30)
  - 1973-1979 publications, 1970-1979 (Box 30)
  - 73-79, 1973-1974, undated (Box 30)
  - 1980s publications, 1981-1988, undated (Box 30)
  - Re-file, 1969-1975, undated (Box 30)
  - Run Through Rock, 2001; 2 (Box 30)
  - Selections of Selected Poems in Run Through Rock by C.D. Wright, 1973-2006, undated (Box 30)
  - Tear sheets / xeroxes, 1972, undated (Box 30)
  - Tear sheets, 1972-2000, undated; 2 (Box 30)
  - Poems + tear sheets, undated (Box 30)
  - Oversize
    - Ringling Suite. Relief Prints and Poems., 2012 (Box 31 (Oversize))
  - Restricted Fragile Material
    Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - LR Brigham book, undated (Box 32)
      2012-ycal-83-0001
- October 2012 Acquisition, 1923-2012; 18.63; (24 boxes)
  Box 55 (audiovisual material): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Box 56 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies of electronic files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  The October 2012 acquisition contains correspondence, writings, audiovisual materials (including sound recordings and photographs), printed material, computer files (including email), and other documents relating chiefly to C. D. Wright's literary and professional activities.
  Former call number: Uncat MSS 1287.
  - Blurbs, recs, nominations '06, 2006, undated (Box 33)
  - Correspondence '06, 2003-2008, undated; 2 (Box 33)
  - Penelope Creeley, 2004-2005, undated (Box 33)
  - MacArthur 2004, 2004, undated (Box 33)
    Includes 1 computer disk
    2012-ycal-82-0001: MacArthur Fellows' Biographies, 1981-2004
  - Miscellaneous notes, addresses, to-do lists, 2004, undated (Box 33)
  - National Bank Award, 2006, undated (Box 33)
  - Pamir's Poetry Journey 2006, 2004-2007, undated (Box 33)
  - Completed '05, '06, 2005-2006, undated (Box 33)
  - Calendar/PR, 2004-2007, undated (Box 33)
  - Completed 2005, 2005, undated (Box 33)
  - 2004 completed, 2004, undated; 2 (Box 33)
  - Completed 03, 2002-2005 (Box 33)
  - PR related 2003 (Box 33)
  - PR related to file 1999-2002 (Box 33)
  - Miscellaneous publications, 1985-2007 (Box 33)
    Includes 9 computer disks
    2102-ycal-82-0002: C. D. Wright syllabi...
    2012-ycal-82-0003: Besmiv selection
    2012-ycal-82-0004: Nov 03 desktop/laptop from 100 zips, broken?
    2012-ycal-82-0005: Old computer, cw matters, students (recs)...
    2012-ycal-82-0006: fall 03 CD
    2012-ycal-82-0007: office omputer files 10-01 CD2
    2012-ycal-82-0008: PWA Disk#4, comashining, Peter Armitogu
    2012-ycal-82-0009: Steal away/corrected 8-22-07 (microsoft word 98)
    2012-ycal-82-0010: Tom Stanley, Floating
  - News/clippings, 2006-2007, undated (Box 33)
  - War 07, 2007 (Box 33)
  - Reviews, 2007, undated (Box 34)
  - Cold cases LC, 2003-2004 (Box 34)
  - Deepstep Come Shining (Box 34)
  - Rising Falling MS, 2003 (Box 34)
  - Rising, Falling, Hovering book MS, undated (Box 34)
  - Rising, Falling, Hovering MSS preliminary, undated (Box 34)
  - Proofs: Like Something Flying Backwards, 2006; 3 (Box 34)
  - One Big Self, proofs (Box 34)
  - One Big Self, 3rd proofs, 2004-2006 (Box 34)
  - Like Something Christenberry pictured 07, 2007 (Box 34)
  - 40 Watts, drafts, 07 (Box 34)
  - Vittista project, early draft, undated (Box 34)
  - Rising, Falling, Hovering, drafts, undated (Box 34)
  - Other people's manuscripts/writings--Johnson Menton, undated (Box 34)
  - Poetry & Violence - Portugal talk - May 07 speech & notes, undated (Box 34)
  - Interviews, undated (Box 34)
  - Correspondence, 1988-2007 (Box 34)
  - Writing - poems in magazines/07 anthologized, 2007 (Box 34)
  - Brown business, 2006-2007 (Box 34)
  - Copper Canyon, 2005-2006, undated (Box 34)
  - Recommendations, tenure review, nominations, etc., 2006-2007 (Box 34)
  - Blurbs/intro, 2007, undated (Box 35)
  - in: completed 06, 2006, undated (Box 35)
  - Completed 07 events, readings, 2006-2007 (Box 35)
  - Solicitations, 2002-2006 (Box 35)
  - Senior project, 2006-2007 (Box 35)
  - Cooling Time, design, 2004, undated (Box 35)
  - Notes, 2007, undated (Box 35)
  - Cards from friends, family, students, colleagues & fans, 1986-2011; 4 (Box 35)
  - Appraisal info Lost Roads Project, 1995-1996 (Box 35)
  - Brown events 2011 (Box 35)
  - Colonies. The Gregor von Rezzori and Beatrice Monti della Corte Retreat for Writers and Botanists, 2002-2005 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence, 1984-2011; 3 (Box 35)
  - Correspondence/play Joan Williams' son, 2005, undated (Box 36)
    2012-ycal-82-0011: Play
  - Creeley promotional, 2005, undated (Box 36)
  - Drafts, undated (Box 36)
  - 2011 translation CDW El dia del judicio volerte mejor caso, undated (Box 36)
  - Family documents, 1966-2002, undated (Box 36)
  - 2010-2011 Ashur Griffith (Box 36)
    2012-ycal-82-0012: Trusting in the Haptic Sense...
  - Images, 2005-2007, undated (Box 36)
  - Judge Shelley Memorial Award with Lyn Hejinian 2008 (Box 36)
  - Judge Typed Press Competition, 2008 (Box 36)
  - Leonore Marshall Poetry Prize 2011 (Box 36)
  - Libya, 2008, undated (Box 36)
  - Mujer, Valerie, undated (Box 36)
  - Misc., 2006-2011, undated (Box 36)
  - Misc. contracts, 2007-2008, undated (Box 36)
  - Ms for Ashanta, 2008 (Box 36)
  - National Books Critics Award, 2010-2011 (Box 36)
  - Nominations, recs, blurbs, 2008-2011 (Box 36)
  - Shall Cross--June 2011 draft (Box 36)
  - Notes, undated (Box 36)
  - PR events 2008, undated (Box 36)
  - Steal Away, reviews, 2001-2005, undated (Box 36)
  - Shelby, 2008 (Box 36)
  - Writing 2011 (Box 36)
  - 92nd St Y, 2011 (Box 36)
  - Cards and personal letters, 2009-2010, undated; 2 (Box 36)
  - Correspondence 2010, 2010, undated; 3 (Box 37)
  - Duvernoy, John, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Gatza, Geoffrey, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Heaney, undated (Box 37)
  - Merwin, W.S., 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Napa 2010, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - PR some reviews, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - NEA Sept 2010, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - NOLA Project: misc. & photos, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - NOLA Project: bibliography, notes on NOLA, undated (Box 37)
  - NOLA Project: Breathtaken drafts, undated (Box 37)
  - NOLA Project: NOLA journals, articles, 1998-2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Professional misc., 2009-2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Refs, refer, blurbs, etc., 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Slovenia, undated (Box 37)
  - Dorothy Tanning 2009 (Box 37)
  - Valerie, undated; 2 (Box 37)
  - Waldrop, 2011 October (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: A Farm Boy manuscript, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: Deepstep 2010 correspondence, 2010-2011 (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: Listening to John (Wright. CD) forward to John Taggerts "Is Music", 2007, undated (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: Rising, Falling, Hovering 2009-2010 reviews from Harvard, Radcliff, Amazon, the New York Times (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: 2010 hand notes calendars, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Wright, C.D.: Writing a Word, Changing It. A draft of an essay on Jean Valentine, undated (Box 37)
  - Zurita, 2010, undated (Box 37)
  - Rhode Island Council for the Humanities (RICH), undated (Box 38)
  - Burt on CD/photography, undated (Box 38)
  - Brown/calendar 09, 2009 (Box 38)
  - China, 2006 (Box 38)
  - Cooling Time, reviews, responses, 2005-2009, undated (Box 38)
  - Correspondences, 2002-2009; 2 (Box 38)
  - 09 events, 2009, undated (Box 38)
  - Griffin Prize, 2009, undated (Box 38)
  - Longenbach online CD, undated (Box 38)
  - Mann, Sally, 2004-2009, undated (Box 38)
    2012-ycal-82-0013: Mann Working Images, 10/3/08, Gagosian
  - Mexico, 2003-2004 (Box 38)
  - Notes, undated (Box 38)
  - Nuptials Oxford Am. Deb and Kevin's wedding, 2008, undated (Box 38)
  - One Big Self, an investigation, 2007, undated (Box 38)
  - Publications 2009 (Box 38)
  - Rees, undated (Box 38)
  - Rising Falling Hovering, 2008-2009 (Box 38)
  - Silliman's Blog response to: Rising Falling Hovering, 2005-2007 (Box 38)
  - Sophi Acad, 2004 (Box 38)
  - Taggart/foreword, undated (Box 38)
  - Alhambra Poetry Calendar, 2007-2008; 2 (Box 38)
    Includes 3 computer disks
    2012-ycal-82-0014: Brom/CD/48...
    2012-ycal-82-0015: Wright
    2012-ycal-82-0016: backup [?] desktop, 1-7-03
  - Poetry Speaks - the Poetry Lovers Calendar, 2008 (Box 39)
  - AAAC C.D. Wright introduction, 2005-2006 (Box 39)
  - An evening with the press Feb. 26, 08, 2007 (Box 39)
  - Arellano 1999 (Box 39)
  - Robert Ashley 2011, 2009-2010 (Box 39)
  - AWP 08, 2008, undated (Box 39)
  - Bei Dao 2011 Graduation Honorary Degree CD Wright as Escourt (Box 39)
  - Blurbs, 2006, undated (Box 39)
  - Boston Review, reviews, 2008 (Box 39)
  - Broadsides, 2007, undated (Box 39)
  - Catalogue of lit. archive CDW, undated (Box 39)
  - Commencement Brown U 2009 (Box 39)
  - Correspondence, misc., 1985-2011, undated; 3 (Box 39)
  - Correspondences II, misc., 1985-2011, undated (Box 39)
  - Creeley, Robert in memorium, undated (Box 39)
  - Dalkey, 2006 (Box 39)
  - England Fall 07, 2007 (Box 39)
  - Events, 2004-2007 (Box 39)
  - Thalion Field promo 2003, undated (Box 39)
  - Carolyn Forche outside reviews 08, 2008, undated (Box 39)
  - Guggenheim recs 2007 (Box 39)
  - Honor. deg. nomin. CD 2011, 2002-2001, undated (Box 39)
  - Judging 2002, 2002-2003 (Box 39)
  - Parnassus rev. 2005 (Box 39)
  - Photos, undated (Box 39)
  - Postcards for Xmas 07, 2007 (Box 39)